cpagrip.com 2019-02-19

# CPAGrip.com - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (together with our terms of use, which are available at <https://www.cpagrip.com/terms.php> governs the manner in which Gripped Media LLC ("CPAGrip") collects, uses, maintains and discloses personal data collected from users as well as all websites working directly or indirectly with the CPAGrip Network. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Gripped Media.

##### Personal Data on website

Gripped Media fully respects your right to privacy and will collect personal data from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. Personal data that we collect about you may include your name, email address, telephone number, instant messenger, social account, home/office address and bank details. Any personal data which you volunteer to Gripped Media will be treated strictly in accordance with the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003. You may refuse to supply personal data to us, except that it may prevent you from engaging in certain Site related activities.

##### Non-personally identifiable information

We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you whenever you interact with our Site. Non-personally identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

##### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to distinguish you from other users of the Site and to enhance your experience when using the Site. Cookies may be placed by your browser on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about your use of the Site. You may choose to set your web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you do so, please note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

##### How we use collected information

Gripped Media may collect and use Users personal information (only on the www.cpagrip.com website, not other websites where we serve our ads) for the following purposes:

\- Business partnerships and co operation

In order for us to engage in business activities with publishers and advertisers, Personal Data will be requested in order to create business related activities such as emails, inquiries and payments

\- To send periodic emails,

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails you can make a request at network@cpagrip.com

\- To personalize user experience,

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

\- Safety,

As part of our efforts to keep the Site safe and secure.

##### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and your browser happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

##### Sharing your personal information

We may disclose your personal data to third parties:

• Gripped Media all or part of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

• If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Website terms of use and other agreements, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our customers and others.

##### Sharing your non-personally identifiable information

• Where we engage trusted third parties to provide services in connection with the Site or our advertising activities.

• Cross reference of user device data for advertising preferences and exclusions

• For screening of fraud and false advertising activities

##### Advertising

Ads appearing on our network may be delivered to you by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement and to compile non personally identifiable information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

The cookies placed by Gripped Media are for attribution (conversion tracking) and frequency capping only. They automatically expire after 28 days.

Gripped Media fully complies and adheres to the principles of DMA and ICO and we simply never store any personal information when showing our ads to any visitors for more than 12 months.

In order to prevent fraud and attribute clicks and conversions, we may collect certain device information including the following:

• Name and properties of mobile applications/websites through which a consumer interacts with the Services;

• Country

• IP Address – hashed version

• Internet browser user-agent used to access the Services; and

• Identifier for advertisers (IFA) / GoogleADID

##### Opt-Out:

All the data we collect is for fraud prevention and conversions attribution only. We don’t use interest based advertising nor retargeting.

To opt-out of our collection of information from mobile devices, please visit your device’s settings to set the "Limit Ad Track" or other similar feature on your device. You can also make choices about data collection for certain companies by visiting http://preferences-mgr.truste.com.

Note that if you opt-out you will still see advertising on your device. In addition, if you reset your device identifier or use a different device you may need to renew your opt-out.

Your Access and Amendment Rights

You have the right, subject to certain exemptions, to obtain a copy of any personal data which we hold about you (for which we may charge you a small fee of $4.99) and to have inaccuracies in the information corrected and to request that we restrict or block the processing of your personal data. If you wish to avail of any of these rights, please contact our data protection officer at network@cpagrip.com

##### Changes to this privacy policy

Gripped Media has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site and revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage you to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

Your continued use of the Site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

##### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of and consent to the practices described in this policy and terms of use (https://www.cpaprip.com/terms.php ). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

Updated: 5/24/2018
